OKPALA CHISOM SHERYL

okpalachisom22@gmail.com +234 (0) 803 781 8417 Abuja, Nigeria

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A creative content writer and digital marketing erudite with 2 years of experience in the past paced industry of media and advertising, with a track record of providing innovative content solutions and strategies for business branding and visibility.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Content creation Digital marketing Stellar research Storytelling Public speaking Marketing

Innovative problem solving Creative writing Brand management

Critical thinking Excellent written and oral communication Social media management

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Muzzlab Technologies

Content writer and Digital marketer

May 2021- Date

- Creating content for client's social media pages and website content.
- Platform management
- Strategy and brainstorming ideas (responsible for rebranding a digital design company to a digital branding agency).

Benin City, Edo State

Ace Farming Abuja, Nigeria

Content writer November -December 2020

Oversaw the general content management of Ace Farming.

Specialized in providing written and video contents for Ace Farming.

MOBicure Benin City, Edo State Content writer January -June 2020

- Provided daily contents across Mobicure's social media platforms and Apps.
- Oversaw content management
- Drove promotional marketing and advertising
- Launched the first Podcast series at Mobicure

Intern October - November 2019

- Oversaw a team of interns to increase the company's branding through effective publicity and programs
- Assisted in the emergence of the Tele-Medicine acclaimed app "Mypaddi"
- Planned programs that emphasized on massive outreach, publicity and health campaigns.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE AND INTERNSHIPS

Digital marketing intern, Side hustle June - July 2021 Illusion Decals January - April 2021

2020 - Date Talent mine academy 2020 - Date Content writer, Jeff Issessele Foundation

EDUCATION

B.Ed. English and Literature Education. <i>University of Benin, Edo State Nigeria.</i>	2019

Introduction to Digital Marketing. SARMLIFE Digital School. 2021

2021 Creative Writing. SARMLIFE Digital School.